{
  "status": {
    "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 0,
    "velocity": 0.5,
    "popularity": 2.808787849598455,
    "pornRank": 0,
    "bozoRank": 0,
    "lastParse": 1476944901,
    "period": 900,
    "lastMaintenanceAt": 1476932642,
    "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
    "lastFetch": 1476944901,
    "code": 200,
    "title": "The GitHub Blog",
    "nextFetch": 1476945801,
    "http": "Fetched (ring) 200 900 and parsed 0/15 entries"
  },
  "title": "The GitHub Blog",
  "updated": "",
  "standardLinks": {},
  "items": [{
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2267",
    "title": "Introducing GitHub Community Guidelines",
    "summary": "We want the GitHub community to be a welcoming environment where people feel empowered to share their opinion and are now accepting feedback on proposed GitHub Community Guidelines.",
    "content": "<p>Building software should be safe for everyone. The GitHub community is made up of millions of developers around the world, ranging from the new developer who created their first \"Hello World\" project to the most well-known software developers in the world. We want the GitHub community to be a welcoming environment where people feel empowered to share their opinion and aren't silenced by fear or shouted down.</p>\n\n<p>Beginning today, we will be accepting feedback on <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/\">proposed GitHub Community Guidelines</a>. By outlining what we expect to see within our community, we hope to help you understand how best to collaborate on GitHub and what type of actions or content may violate our <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/#legal-notices\">Terms of Service</a>. The policy consist of four parts:</p>\n\n<ol>\n<li><p><a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/#building-a-strong-community\">Best practices for building a strong community</a> - people are encouraged to be welcoming, assume no malice, stay on topic, and use clear and concise language at all times.</p></li>\n<li><p><a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/#what-if-something-or-someone-offends-you\">What to do if something offends you</a> - project maintainers are encouraged to communicate expectations and to moderate comments within their community — including locking conversations or blocking users when necessary.</p></li>\n<li><p><a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/#what-is-not-allowed\">What behavior is not allowed on GiHub</a> - the community will not tolerate threats of violence, hate speech, bullying, harassment, impersonation, invasions of privacy, sexually explicit content, or active malware.</p></li>\n<li><p><a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/github-community-guidelines/#what-happens-if-someone-breaks-the-rules\">What happens if someone breaks the rules</a> - GitHub may block or remove content and may terminate or suspend accounts that violate these rules.</p></li>\n</ol>\n\n<p>As always, we will continue to investigate any abuse reports and may moderate public content on our site that we determine to be in violation of our Terms of Service. To be clear, GitHub does not actively seek out content to moderate. Instead, we rely on community members like you to communicate expectations, moderate projects, and <a href=\"https://github.com/contact/report-abuse\">report abusive behavior or content</a>.</p>\n\n<p>Additionally, we are releasing the guidelines under <a href=\"https://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/\">the Creative Commons Zero License</a> in hopes of encouraging other platforms to establish similar norms to govern their respective communities.</p>\n\n<p>These guidelines are first and foremost <em>community</em> guidelines and we'd like to hear your thoughts on them before they're finalized. Please <a href=\"https://github.com/contact/community-guidelines\">get in touch with us with any feedback or questions</a> prior to November 20th, 2016. Together, we can make the open source community a healthy, inclusive place we can all be proud of.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1476835329,
    "updated": 1476835329,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Introducing GitHub Community Guidelines",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2267-introducing-github-community-guidelines",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Introducing GitHub Community Guidelines",
        "href": "https://avatars0.githubusercontent.com/u/2433775?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2267-introducing-github-community-guidelines",
    "categories": ["general"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "balevine",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "balevine"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1476835329,
      "updated": 1476835329,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.5,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.808787849598455,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1476835,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1476759,
        "lastFetch": 1476835,
        "nextFetch": 1476836,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2266",
    "title": "New to InnerSource? At GitHub Universe, a Panel of Experts Talk Through the Corporate Version of Open Source",
    "content": "<p>Most developers are already familiar with the concept of InnerSourcing, although many have never called it that. InnerSource is simply using best practices and methodologies from open source development in a confined corporate environment. Several large organizations have already embraced these processes to great advantage, and a few of them came together at GitHub Universe to discuss how their teams are benefitting. </p>\n\n<p>Kakul Srivastava, VP of Product Management at GitHub, moderated a panel featuring Panna Pavangadkar, Global Head of Engineering Developer Experience at Bloomberg, Yasuhiro Inami, iOS Engineer at Line, Joan Watson, Director of Engineering IT at Hewlett-Packard Enterprise, Jeremy King, Senior Vice President and CTO for Global eCommerce at Walmart, and Jeff Jagoda, Senior Software Engineer at IBM. </p>\n\n<p>During the course of the 45-minute discussion, panelists offered anecdotes and examples of the many positive ways InnerSource practices have impacted their teams — not a small feat when it comes to enacting change in highly structured, highly distributed companies with thousands of developers all over the world. Across the board, panelists reported seeing not only increased collaboration between previously siloed teams, but also a reduction in bottlenecks, as well as increased communication on projects. </p>\n\n<p>“Once you embrace it [InnerSource] and see new teams come on, you show examples of places where not only can people contribute, you unlock bottlenecks,” said Walmart’s Jeremy King. “When you're working with large software companies, on lots of different projects, you end up having inherent bottlenecks in some team or another — and it’s awesome to have another team come in and say, ‘I can fix this bug’ or ‘I can add this feature’, without impacting the overall roadmap of that important group.”</p>\n\n<p>From shorter shipping times to community development to designing innovative products, InnerSource has evolved the workflow of teams operating on an enormous scale — however, the advantages of the InnerSource process can benefit teams of all sizes by introducing the collaborative and creative principles of open source development. </p>\n\n<p>Learn more about how InnerSource practices can impact your teams by watching the full video below:</p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/sDKN-xyqcNc?list=PL0lo9MOBetEEUcOiXSL0XMRZKfAWlZ3Cb\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1476397510,
    "updated": 1476397510,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "New to InnerSource? At GitHub Universe, a Panel of Experts Talk Through the Corporate Version of Open Source",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2266-new-to-innersource-at-github-universe-a-panel-of-experts-talk-through-the-corporate-version-of-open-source",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "New to InnerSource? At GitHub Universe, a Panel of Experts Talk Through the Corporate Version of Open Source",
        "href": "https://avatars3.githubusercontent.com/u/16549281?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2266-new-to-innersource-at-github-universe-a-panel-of-experts-talk-through-the-corporate-version-of-open-source",
    "categories": ["conferences"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "kdraps",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "kdraps"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1476397510,
      "updated": 1476397510,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 2,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.6,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.81308098290988,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1476397,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1476325,
        "lastFetch": 1476397,
        "nextFetch": 1476398,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2264",
    "title": "Get testing with Taplytics in the Student Developer Pack",
    "content": "<p><a href=\"https://taplytics.com/\">Taplytics</a> is now offering mobile testing to students in the Student Developer Pack.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/18125109/19159686/02366b44-8bb3-11e6-98c1-6078356c5055.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/18125109/19159686/02366b44-8bb3-11e6-98c1-6078356c5055.png\" alt=\"Taplytics joins the Student Developer Pack\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>Taplytics helps mobile developers create great experiences through: A/B testing, push notifications, and custom analytics. As part of the <a href=\"https://education.github.com/pack\">GitHub Student Developer Pack</a>, Taplytics will give you complete access to its suite of tools for native mobile apps. </p>\n\n<p>For members of the pack Taplytics is offering full, unlimited access to the platform free for 6 months. You will be able to do visual tests on your apps and make design decisions that work best for your users. You’ll be able to get analytics around your apps that help you iterate on your app in the future. Taplytics also includes tools that help you provide users with the right information at the right time.</p>\n\n<p>The Student Developer Pack gives students free access to the best developer tools from different technology companies like Datadog, Travis CI, and Unreal Engine. </p>\n\n<p>Students, get testing now with your <a href=\"https://education.github.com/pack\">pack</a>.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1476373330,
    "updated": 1476373331,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Get testing with Taplytics in the Student Developer Pack",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2264-get-testing-with-taplytics-in-the-student-developer-pack",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Get testing with Taplytics in the Student Developer Pack",
        "href": "https://avatars3.githubusercontent.com/u/17101092?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2264-get-testing-with-taplytics-in-the-student-developer-pack",
    "categories": ["general"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "fossygirl",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "fossygirl"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1476373331,
      "updated": 1476373331,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.6,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.81308098290988,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1476373,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1476325,
        "lastFetch": 1476373,
        "nextFetch": 1476374,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2265",
    "title": "Dismissing reviews on Pull Requests",
    "content": "<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/98681/19321785/3ad41962-906b-11e6-9320-f24bf164e17e.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/98681/19321785/3ad41962-906b-11e6-9320-f24bf164e17e.png\" alt=\"Dismiss reviews on GitHub\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-request-reviews/\">Pull request reviews</a> are a great way to share the weight of building software. Using <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/about-protected-branches/\">protected branches</a> to block merging when pull requests have reviews that request changes helps keep your team maintain quality, bug-free code. However, this requirement can sometimes block your team’s progress without good reason. If someone leaves a review that requests changes and then goes on vacation or runs into computer problems, your pull request could be blocked for days, even after you’ve addressed the reviewer’s concerns.</p>\n\n<p>To improve this workflow, we’re adding the ability for pull request collaborators to <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/dismissing-a-pull-request-review\">dismiss reviews</a>. When someone leaves a review that requests changes, dismissing the review changes it from a review that requests changes to a review comment. This will unblock your pull request, freeing you up to merge it!</p>\n\n<p>You can also dismiss an approving review. This is useful when your pull request has changed significantly since the approval, and you think it’s important to get another review.</p>\n\n<p>When one of your team members dismisses a review, they’ll have to leave a reason why. This keeps people from simply bypassing the protected branch review requirement out of convenience.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1476295111,
    "updated": 1476295302,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Dismissing reviews on Pull Requests",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2265-dismissing-reviews-on-pull-requests",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Dismissing reviews on Pull Requests",
        "href": "https://avatars1.githubusercontent.com/u/3522670?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2265-dismissing-reviews-on-pull-requests",
    "categories": ["ship"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "nplasterer",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "nplasterer"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1476295302,
      "updated": 1476295302,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.5,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.813867758788755,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (ring) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1476295,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1476238,
        "lastFetch": 1476295,
        "nextFetch": 1476296,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2262",
    "title": "GitHub's game jam, Game Off, returns next month",
    "content": "<p><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/121322/19134164/3813bd04-8b11-11e6-8553-30f566029e1b.png\" alt=\"GitHub Game Off - Game Jam Hackathon Logo\" style=\"border:0;\"></p>\n\n<p>The GitHub Game Off, our very own game jam, returns next month! Participants will have the entire month of November to build a game based on a secret theme (to be announced later) and share their creations with the world.</p>\n\n<p>Much like previous years, the use of open source engines, libraries, and tools is encouraged, but not a strict requirement. Unlike previous years, however, we're removing the restrictions! Previously you could only submit web-based games, but now all games are welcome - all platforms, operating systems, and devices.</p>\n\n<p>The theme for this year's Game Off will be announced here on the GitHub blog on Nov 1st at 13:37 PDT, so please stay tuned.</p>\n\n<p>We've seen some <a href=\"https://github.com/showcases/game-off-winners\">great games submitted in previous years</a>. We can't wait to see what you come up with this year &lt;3</p>\n\n<iframe width=\"685\" height=\"385\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/uG1zzGNPDnU\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>\n\n<p>The official Twitter hashtag for the Game Off is <a href=\"https://twitter.com/hashtag/ggo16\"><code>#ggo16</code></a>.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1475858839,
    "updated": 1475858839,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "GitHub's game jam, Game Off, returns next month",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2262-github-s-game-jam-game-off-returns-next-month",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "GitHub's game jam, Game Off, returns next month",
        "href": "https://avatars2.githubusercontent.com/u/121322?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2262-github-s-game-jam-game-off-returns-next-month",
    "categories": ["general"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "leereilly",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "leereilly"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1475858839,
      "updated": 1475858839,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.5,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.7943267604680098,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1475858,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1475805,
        "lastFetch": 1475858,
        "nextFetch": 1475859,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2260",
    "title": "Hacktoberfest is back",
    "content": "<p><a href=\"https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/121322/18864038/31532b4a-8449-11e6-8701-97c00c95bf09.png\" alt=\"Hacktoberfest 2016\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>Celebrate open source this October by participating in <a href=\"https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com\">Hacktoberfest</a>, a month-long festival of code organized by our friends at DigitalOcean and hosted on GitHub.</p>\n\n<p>To participate, simply open a pull request and contribute to any open source project. You can fix a bug, add a feature, or even improve some documentation. If you've never contributed to an open source project before, check out our <a href=\"https://guides.github.com/activities/contributing-to-open-source/\">contributing to open source guide</a>. </p>\n\n<p>Once you've made your contribution, tell the world about it with the <code>#hacktoberfest</code> hashtag on <a href=\"https://twitter.com/hashtag/hacktoberfest\">Twitter</a>, <a href=\"https://www.facebook.com/hashtag/hacktoberfest\">Facebook</a>, or <a href=\"https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/hacktoberfest/\">Instagram</a>. <g-emoji alias=\"tada\" fallback-src=\"https://assets-cdn.github.com/images/icons/emoji/unicode/1f389.png\">🎉</g-emoji> </p>\n\n<p>If you make four pull requests by October 31st, you'll get the satisfaction of sharing your code with the world—and a t-shirt, of course. </p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/121322/18863744/d18725f0-8447-11e6-9673-503471e4dd54.png\" alt=\"Hacktoberfest 2016 t-shirt\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>To make your mark on open source (and secure your Hacktoberfest t-shirt) please visit <a href=\"https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/\">https://hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/</a> for more details.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1474994717,
    "updated": 1474994717,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Hacktoberfest is back",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2260-hacktoberfest-is-back",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Hacktoberfest is back",
        "href": "https://avatars2.githubusercontent.com/u/121322?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2260-hacktoberfest-is-back",
    "categories": ["general"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "leereilly",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "leereilly"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1474994717,
      "updated": 1474994717,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.6,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.7784421709680855,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1474994,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1474937,
        "lastFetch": 1474994,
        "nextFetch": 1474995,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2243",
    "title": "Rebase and merge pull requests",
    "content": "<p>The merge button on pull requests supports two great workflows\nwith merge commits and <a href=\"https://github.com/blog/2141-squash-your-commits\">commit squashing</a>.\nNow you can use the merge button to rebase and merge your changes, too.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/2195/18794869/3b06b4ee-81b1-11e6-96f8-f7b34eb30b05.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/2195/18794869/3b06b4ee-81b1-11e6-96f8-f7b34eb30b05.png\" alt=\"Rebase\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<h2>\n<a id=\"how-does-it-work\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#how-does-it-work\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>How does it work?</h2>\n\n<p>When you select the new \"Rebase and merge\" option,\nthe commits from the pull request's branch are rebased on to the tip\nof the base branch, and then the base branch itself is fast forwarded\nto this newly rebased head. Rebases automatically set the committer of\nthe rebased commits to the current user, while keeping authorship\ninformation intact.\nThe pull request's branch will not be modified by this operation.</p>\n\n<p>If a rebase can't be performed due to conflicts, we'll let you know so\nyou can manually resolve them as necessary.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/2195/18671961/a03fa9b6-7f35-11e6-8fa0-e16b2fede8ca.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/2195/18671961/a03fa9b6-7f35-11e6-8fa0-e16b2fede8ca.gif\" alt=\"Rebase with conflicts\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>As with \"Squash and merge\", repository administrators can decide whether they\nwant to allow this new option on the repository settings page.</p>\n\n<p>Learn more about <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-request-merges#rebase-and-merge-your-pull-request-commits\">rebase and merge</a> in our Help docs.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1474897220,
    "updated": 1474897220,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Rebase and merge pull requests",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2243-rebase-and-merge-pull-requests",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Rebase and merge pull requests",
        "href": "https://avatars0.githubusercontent.com/u/2195?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2243-rebase-and-merge-pull-requests",
    "categories": ["ship"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "arthurschreiber",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "arthurschreiber"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1474897220,
      "updated": 1474897220,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.5,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.771935745520095,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (ring) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1474897,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1474851,
        "lastFetch": 1474897,
        "nextFetch": 1474898,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2252",
    "title": "License now displayed on repository overview",
    "content": "<p>Licenses are now displayed in the repository overview, allowing anyone to easily see if a project has an open source license. This change is immediately available on GitHub, and will also ship with the upcoming <a href=\"https://enterprise.github.com/home\">Enterprise</a> 2.8 release.</p>\n\n<p>A shortened license name, linking to the repository’s license file, is displayed on the repository page:</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/731773/18727946/1aa7b2fa-8019-11e6-84bd-178f93bcd8ee.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/731773/18727946/1aa7b2fa-8019-11e6-84bd-178f93bcd8ee.png\" alt=\"screenshot\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>We use an open source Ruby gem called <a href=\"https://github.com/benbalter/licensee\">Licensee</a> to compare the repository's LICENSE file to a short list of known licenses. This is the same code we use to provide the <a href=\"https://developer.github.com/v3/licenses/\">Licenses API</a> and <a href=\"https://github.com/blog/1964-open-source-license-usage-on-github-com\">understand how repositories on GitHub are licensed</a>.</p>\n\n<p>We don’t detect every open source license, nor complicated situations such as projects with multiple licenses. For those situations you can still find and read the project’s license(s) as before.</p>\n\n<p>Open source is a fundamental part of GitHub’s community. Adding an open source license to your repository ensures that others can use, copy, modify, and contribute back to your project. It's an important step when creating an open source project. If your repository doesn’t have an open source license and you want others to get involved, consider <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/open-source-licensing/\">adding one now</a>.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1474490364,
    "updated": 1474490364,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "License now displayed on repository overview",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2252-license-now-displayed-on-repository-overview",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "License now displayed on repository overview",
        "href": "https://avatars3.githubusercontent.com/u/875834?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2252-license-now-displayed-on-repository-overview",
    "categories": ["ship"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "aymannadeem",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "aymannadeem"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1474490364,
      "updated": 1474490364,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.6,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.774205448898533,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1474490,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1474417,
        "lastFetch": 1474490,
        "nextFetch": 1474491,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2259",
    "title": "Mission Report: GitHub Universe",
    "content": "<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/121322/18649301/a9740512-7e73-11e6-8db1-e266cd1c2a3b.jpg\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/121322/18649301/a9740512-7e73-11e6-8db1-e266cd1c2a3b.jpg\" alt=\"Chris Wanstrath Keynote\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>On September 14 in San Francisco, more than 1,500 developers helped us kick off <a href=\"http://githubuniverse.com/\">GitHub Universe</a> and share stories about open source, workplace best practices, and how the GitHub Community builds software. In case you missed it, here are some highlights, along with the new features and community updates announced:</p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/u9s_W8lCrDU?list=PL0lo9MOBetEGkI7QIYnUbDdrSUYokmCUW\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>\n\n<p>We started day one with a keynote by GitHub CEO Chris Wanstrath, who shared a few brand new developments from around the GitHub Universe. We were also joined by CEO of <a href=\"http://www.blackgirlscode.com/\">Black Girl's Code</a> Kimberly Bryant and <a href=\"https://www.whitehouse.gov/administration/eop/oa/divisions/ocio\">White House Senior Technology Officer</a> Alvand Salehi. For more details, <a href=\"https://github.com/blog/2256-a-whole-new-github-universe-announcing-new-tools-forums-and-features\">check out the launch post</a>.</p>\n\n<p>On day two, we heard a keynote from GitHub's VP Social Impact Nicole Sanchez, Dr. Kortney Ziegler, and David Molina of <a href=\"https://operationcode.org/\">Operation Code</a> who shared their thoughts on training new developers and expanding opportunities to participate in technology for people from all backgrounds </p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/0A-u1tQTBqo?list=PL0lo9MOBetEGkI7QIYnUbDdrSUYokmCUW\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"code-review\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#code-review\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Code Review</h3>\n\n<p>Our new Reviews improves code review on GitHub and helps you share the weight of building software. Reviews allow you to comment on specific lines of code, formally “approve” or “request changes” to pull requests, and more. Our initial changes are only the first step of a much greater roadmap toward faster, friendlier code reviews. </p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/HW0RPaJqm4g\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"projects\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#projects\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Projects</h3>\n\n<p>With Projects, you can organize work from your GitHub repositories and integrate project management into your development cycle without skipping a beat (or even opening a new browser tab).</p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/C6MGKHkNtxU\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>\n\n<p>Although we’ll quickly add to Projects, our initial release currently supports:</p>\n\n<ul>\n<li>A New Projects tab–at the same level as Code, Issue, Pull Requests within a repository–that lists all of your projects</li>\n<li>Workflow columns that you can name and reorder</li>\n<li>Cards that you can drag and drop between columns pointing to issues, Pull Requests, or notes</li>\n<li>Tools built on top of Projects by some fantastic partners, including Waffle.io and ZenHub</li>\n</ul>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"platform-updates\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#platform-updates\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Platform updates</h3>\n\n<p>We launched a few things to make integrating with GitHub a better, more enjoyable experience, including <a href=\"https://developer.github.com/early-access/platform-roadmap/\">a public Platform Roadmap</a> and <a href=\"https://platform.github.community/\">the GitHub Platform Forum</a>. We also launched two new projects to make our platform more flexible:</p>\n\n<ul>\n<li>\n<a href=\"https://developer.github.com/changes/2016-09-14-I=integrations-early-access/\"><strong>Integrations Early Access:</strong></a> a new model that provides better ways for tools to extend and integrate with GitHub</li>\n<li>\n<a href=\"http://githubengineering.com/the-github-graphql-api/\"><strong>The GitHub GraphQL API Early Access:</strong></a> a GraphQL API that simplifies product development</li>\n</ul>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"breakout-sessions\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#breakout-sessions\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Breakout sessions</h3>\n\n<p>Our breakout sessions this year covered everything from product updates and applications to building more diverse and inclusive engineering teams. All of the talks from the general sessions are ready for you to <a href=\"https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL0lo9MOBetEGkI7QIYnUbDdrSUYokmCUW\">watch from home</a>—and recordings of the Launch, Flight, and Orbit breakouts will be available soon.  </p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"benefit-concert\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#benefit-concert\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Benefit concert</h3>\n\n<p>We ended Monday at The Masonic with the Big Bang—a benefit concert for <a href=\"http://www.blackgirlscode.com/\">Black Girls Code</a>. Artist and actor COMMON headlined with support from Lion Babe. Head to <a href=\"http://www.blackgirlscode.com\">www.blackgirlscode.com</a> to learn more about BGC's work and find out how you can help them reach their mission to teach one million girls to code. </p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"sponsors\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#sponsors\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Sponsors</h3>\n\n<p>GitHub Universe would not have been possible without the support of our sponsors, who provided food, juice, coffee, bubble tea, and beautiful art installations for our enjoyment. </p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13242718/18066094/b3d4f888-6deb-11e6-8d58-5132bef864ec.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/13242718/18066094/b3d4f888-6deb-11e6-8d58-5132bef864ec.png\" alt=\"Sponsors of GitHub Universe\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"thank-you\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#thank-you\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Thank you</h3>\n\n<p>And finally, thank you to our community for making all of this possible—and helping GitHub Universe take flight. </p>\n\n<iframe width=\"560\" height=\"315\" src=\"https://www.youtube.com/embed/qwLDACQeWBI\" frameborder=\"0\" allowfullscreen></iframe>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1474406601,
    "updated": 1474406601,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "Mission Report: GitHub Universe",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2259-mission-report-github-universe",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "Mission Report: GitHub Universe",
        "href": "https://avatars3.githubusercontent.com/u/7321362?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2259-mission-report-github-universe",
    "categories": ["conferences"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "stephbwills",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "stephbwills"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1474406601,
      "updated": 1474406601,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 1,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.5,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.7733393876650365,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1474406,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1474330,
        "lastFetch": 1474406,
        "nextFetch": 1474407,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }, {
    "id": "tag:github.com,2008:Post/2256",
    "title": "A whole new GitHub Universe: announcing new tools, forums, and features",
    "content": "<p>Today I welcomed more than 1,500 people to <a href=\"http://github.com/universe-2016\">our second annual Universe conference</a> in San Francisco, an event designed to celebrate the people building the future of software. It’s an important reminder about who we’re here for—whether it’s the open source maintainer whose project is transforming healthcare, an automotive company building a self-driving car, or a teenager teaching herself how to program after she finishes her homework.</p>\n\n<p>Our goal is to make building software easier for you. And with that goal in sight, we’re announcing our biggest update to the platform yet. We’re making it easier for you to work together to ship high-quality code through improved code review tools, and we’re giving our profiles an update to better show who you are as a developer. We’re making integrating with GitHub a first class experience through major API improvements. And we’re taking steps toward making GitHub a better place for businesses to get work done with added security measures for organizations.</p>\n\n<p>I’m proud of our team for coming together to ship so many improvements to the platform, and I hope you’ll find them useful as you continue to build amazing things. Read on for more specifics, and keep an eye out for continued improvements to your GitHub experience in the coming months.</p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"manage-your-ideas-with-projects\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#manage-your-ideas-with-projects\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Manage your ideas with Projects</h3>\n\n<p>Taking projects from idea to launch isn’t easy. There’s a lot to coordinate behind the scenes, and <a href=\"https://github.com/integrations/feature/project-management\">so many tools</a> out there to help you organize and distribute work. To help you integrate project management into your development cycle without skipping a beat (or even opening a new browser tab), we’re introducing <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/tracking-the-progress-of-your-work-with-projects\">Projects</a>.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18481731/44629a3e-79ab-11e6-8ce9-9ad5f07a135d.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18481731/44629a3e-79ab-11e6-8ce9-9ad5f07a135d.gif\" alt=\"Projects\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>With Projects, you can manage work directly from your GitHub repositories. Create cards from Pull Requests, Issues or Notes and organize them into custom columns, whether it’s \"In-progress\", \"Done\", \"Never going to happen\" or any other framework your team uses. Drag and drop the cards inside a column to prioritize them or move them from one column to another as your work progresses. And with Notes, you can capture every early idea that comes up as part of your standup or team sync, without polluting your list of issues. For more on what's changing, <a href=\"https://youtu.be/NoBI4_9EuUw\">watch a quick overview</a>.</p>\n\n<p>Although we’ll quickly be adding to Projects, our initial release currently supports:</p>\n\n<ul>\n<li>A New Projects tab–at the same level as Code, Issue, Pull Requests within a repository–that lists all of your projects</li>\n<li>Workflow columns that you can name and reorder</li>\n<li>Cards that you can drag and drop between columns pointing to issues, Pull Requests, or notes</li>\n<li>Tools built on top of Projects by some fantastic partners, including Waffle.io and ZenHub</li>\n</ul>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"code-better-with-reviews\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#code-better-with-reviews\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Code better with Reviews</h3>\n\n<p>Collaboration is the core of building great software—and code review is critical to collaboration. When another person looks at your code and gives it the same level of critique that you did while writing it, your work gets better. We’re improving code review on GitHub to help you share the weight of building software and improve the software you build.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469522/7fb44b30-7976-11e6-9674-8a32a92506ff.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469522/7fb44b30-7976-11e6-9674-8a32a92506ff.gif\" alt=\"GitHub code review\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>Designing the best way for you to review code is a continuous process, but our first step is now available on all pull requests—Reviews. In addition to commenting on specific lines of code, Reviews let you formally “approve” or “request changes” to pull requests. You can also leave a review summary and delete, edit, or bundle comments before you submit them.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469521/7fb32732-7976-11e6-80cf-f2ab37688768.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469521/7fb32732-7976-11e6-80cf-f2ab37688768.gif\" alt=\"Reviewing code changes\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>To streamline conversations and cut down on noise, you can reply to inline comments without drafting a formal review or starting a new conversation. This also means you can have multiple conversations per line of code—creating more explicit feedback loops, smarter conversations, and better code review.</p>\n\n<p>Finally, administrators can require Reviews before merging via <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/about-protected-branches/\">protected branches</a>. When Reviews are required, you must have a least one approval and no changes requested before you can merge.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1369864/18179223/08cc316e-7047-11e6-81dd-f9f70e2b779f.png\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/1369864/18179223/08cc316e-7047-11e6-81dd-f9f70e2b779f.png\" alt=\"Blocked Pull Request\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>These changes are only the first step of a much greater roadmap toward faster, friendlier code reviews. We’re working on a handful of follow-up feature improvements—including the ability to request reviews from your peers. For more information on Reviews, including what we’ve shipped today, check out the <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/reviewing-changes-in-pull-requests\">documentation</a> or <a href=\"https://youtu.be/HW0RPaJqm4g\">a quick tutorial video on Reviews</a>.</p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"integrate-seamlessly-with-github\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#integrate-seamlessly-with-github\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Integrate seamlessly with GitHub</h3>\n\n<p>Developers use a variety of tools to ship their software and we’ve seen <a href=\"https://github.com/github/blog-posts/pull/github.com/integrations\">hundreds of integrations</a> built to work with GitHub. Now we’re shipping some major improvements to our API and adding new ways to collaborate transparently not only with GitHub engineers but also the broader community of integrators. As host to the largest community of developers, we want to make the GitHub platform uniquely enjoyable for integrators to build applications that change how people work. Here’s what we’re launching right away:</p>\n\n<ul>\n<li>\n<a href=\"https://developer.github.com/early-access/platform-roadmap/\">A public Platform Roadmap</a> that demonstrates what GitHub Platform Engineers are launching next and why</li>\n<li>A formalized process to solicit feedback and launch updates to our platform</li>\n<li>Early-access and pre-release programs that let you access new features and APIs and provide you with the support you need to ensure launch readiness for the software you build on top of GitHub</li>\n<li>\n<a href=\"https://platform.github.community/\">The GitHub Platform Forum</a> which provides a direct communication channel between ecosystem developers and GitHub engineers.</li>\n</ul>\n\n<p>With that, we are excited to announce two new projects that aim to make our platform more flexible:</p>\n\n<h4>\n<a id=\"integrations-early-access\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#integrations-early-access\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Integrations Early Access</h4>\n\n<p>We’re rethinking our integrations model to provide better ways for tools to extend and integrate with GitHub. We’ve added the ability for an integration to act on its own behalf instead of impersonating a user—making it a first class actor on GitHub without using a paid seat. Admins will have the ability to configure integrations directly on Organizations and control which repositories they allow access to. Read more about Integrations on our <a href=\"https://developer.github.com/changes/2016-09-14-Integrations-Early-Access/\">Developer Blog</a> or <a href=\"https://developer.github.com/early-access/integrations\">check out the documentation</a>.</p>\n\n<h4>\n<a id=\"the-github-graphql-api-early-access\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#the-github-graphql-api-early-access\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>The GitHub GraphQL API Early Access</h4>\n\n<p>The GraphQL API simplifies your product development by letting developers access all the data they need, and only the data they need, with one API call. With the GitHub GraphQL API, you get the same API we use to build GitHub features. To learn more and see how it works, check out our <a href=\"http://githubengineering.com/the-github-graphql-api/\">Engineering Blog</a>.</p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"have-a-friendlier-business-experience-on-githubcom\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#have-a-friendlier-business-experience-on-githubcom\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Have a friendlier business experience on GitHub.com</h3>\n\n<p>Organizations on GitHub are the best way for teams of developers to build and ship software together, and with the added security of two-factor authentication enforcement and upcoming product enhancements, they’ve never been better.</p>\n\n<h4>\n<a id=\"easily-enforce-security\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#easily-enforce-security\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Easily enforce security</h4>\n\n<p>Now Organization administrators can require <a href=\"https://github.com/blog/1614-two-factor-authentication\">two-factor authentication</a> for all members—making it easier to support security policies.</p>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469880/e252d36e-7977-11e6-9a2a-e3a4a091a8e9.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18469880/e252d36e-7977-11e6-9a2a-e3a4a091a8e9.gif\" alt=\"Enforced two-factor authentication in an organization\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>Admins will be asked to confirm the two-factor authentication requirement and a confirmation modal will list members and forks that will be removed as a result. GitHub will notify members if they’re being removed from an organization with email and in-product notifications. Finally, as always, admins can <a href=\"https://github.com/blog/2215-reinstate-removed-members-to-an-organization\">invite members back with their forks and settings in tact</a> once their security is up to speed. <a href=\"https://help.github.com/articles/requiring-two-factor-authentication-in-your-organization\">Read more</a> about requiring two-factor authentication in your organization. </p>\n\n<h4>\n<a id=\"take-greater-control-over-your-permissions\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#take-greater-control-over-your-permissions\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Take greater control over your permissions</h4>\n\n<p>Over the last few years, we’ve rolled out LDAP and CAS to securely and efficiently manage permissions on GitHub Enterprise. Now we’re making sure businesses on GitHub.com have the tools they need to automate identity and access management. Our first public launch is a SAML-based Single Sign-on (SSO) option. Administrators will have the ability to manage their GitHub users through the identity provider that already manages access to the host of applications they use in their current workflow. This option isn’t ready quite yet, but it will launch as a beta in the coming months. <a href=\"http://github.com/universe-2016#business\">Sign up to try it out when it does</a>.</p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"get-help-from-the-github-community\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#get-help-from-the-github-community\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>Get help from the GitHub Community</h3>\n\n<p>We’re grateful to have a community of more than 16 million developers. While developers gain experience implicitly on GitHub as they work alongside other developers, we know that’s not enough. To help, we’re creating a dedicated space for you to learn from each other—and to have conversations about GitHub itself.</p>\n\n<p>The GitHub Community Forum will become a place where developers can talk shop, get help, and learn together. It will also help us introduce new features and improvements and give developers the ability to share thoughts and feedback with us directly. Look out for the GitHub Community Forum in 2017.</p>\n\n<h3>\n<a id=\"see-whats-behind-your-green-squares\" class=\"anchor\" href=\"#see-whats-behind-your-green-squares\" aria-hidden=\"true\"><span aria-hidden=\"true\" class=\"octicon octicon-link\"></span></a>See what’s behind your green squares</h3>\n\n<p><a href=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18485206/dd215fea-79b9-11e6-8781-1c5915cad384.gif\" target=\"_blank\"><img src=\"https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/3477155/18485206/dd215fea-79b9-11e6-8781-1c5915cad384.gif\" alt=\"New user profiles\" style=\"max-width:100%;\"></a></p>\n\n<p>Your profile now contains your entire history of work on GitHub, from your first commit to your most recent pull request. And a per-repository breakdown reveals where you're spending your time each month. You can see special events in your history—the day you signed up for GitHub, opened your first pull request, or joined an organization—and showcase your best work by pinning favorite projects to your profile. For more on what’s changed, <a href=\"https://help.github.com/categories/setting-up-and-managing-your-github-profile\">take a look at the documentation</a> or <a href=\"https://youtu.be/IyUqdPNMZME\">watch the video</a>.</p>\n\n<p>While I’m really excited about these improvements to GitHub, I’m more excited to see what you’ll create with them.</p>",
    "language": "en",
    "published": 1473876850,
    "updated": 1473876850,
    "standardLinks": {
      "alternate": [{
        "title": "A whole new GitHub Universe: announcing new tools, forums, and features",
        "href": "https://github.com/blog/2256-a-whole-new-github-universe-announcing-new-tools-forums-and-features",
        "rel": "alternate",
        "type": "text/html"
      }],
      "thumbnail": [{
        "title": "A whole new GitHub Universe: announcing new tools, forums, and features",
        "href": "https://avatars3.githubusercontent.com/u/2?v=3&s=60",
        "rel": "thumbnail",
        "type": "image/jpeg"
      }]
    },
    "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog/2256-a-whole-new-github-universe-announcing-new-tools-forums-and-features",
    "categories": ["ship"],
    "actor": {
      "id": "defunkt",
      "language": "en",
      "displayName": "defunkt"
    },
    "source": {
      "id": "tag:github.com,2008:/blog",
      "title": "The GitHub Blog",
      "language": "en-us",
      "published": 1473876850,
      "updated": 1473876850,
      "standardLinks": {
        "alternate": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog",
          "rel": "alternate",
          "type": "text/html"
        }],
        "self": [{
          "title": "The GitHub Blog",
          "href": "https://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "self",
          "type": "application/atom+xml"
        }],
        "superfeedr": [{
          "href": "http://github.com/blog.atom",
          "rel": "superfeedr"
        }]
      },
      "permalinkUrl": "https://github.com/blog",
      "status": {
        "entriesCountSinceLastMaintenance": 3,
        "period": 900,
        "velocity": 0.6,
        "pornRank": 0,
        "bozoRank": 0,
        "popularity": 2.7457158361229874,
        "code": "200",
        "http": "Fetched (selfPing) 200 900 and parsed 1/15 entries",
        "lastParse": 1473876,
        "lastMaintenanceAt": 1473810,
        "lastFetch": 1473876,
        "nextFetch": 1473877,
        "feed": "http://github.com/blog.atom"
      }
    }
  }]
}
